{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382841559","data":{"timestamp":" 947382841558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_045338"," gameId":" 334a5258-4202-4205-8b74-dcc205feb566"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_bwa-nji-mfa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382846602","data":{"timestamp":" 947382846602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_045338"," gameId":" 334a5258-4202-4205-8b74-dcc205feb566"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mgu_nje-nja-mgu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mgu"," userResponse":" mgu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382853084","data":{"timestamp":" 947382853084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_045338"," gameId":" 334a5258-4202-4205-8b74-dcc205feb566"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndu_ndu-chi-nyi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndu"," userResponse":" ndu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382859848","data":{"timestamp":" 947382859848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_045338"," gameId":" 334a5258-4202-4205-8b74-dcc205feb566"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nja_mwo-vya-nja"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382867362","data":{"timestamp":" 947382867362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_045338"," gameId":" 334a5258-4202-4205-8b74-dcc205feb566"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpi_mpi-bwa-cha"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpi"," userResponse":" mpi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382874392","data":{"timestamp":" 947382874392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_045338"," gameId":" 334a5258-4202-4205-8b74-dcc205feb566"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_thi_njo-swa-thi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" thi"," userResponse":" thi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382880253","data":{"timestamp":" 947382880252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_045338"," gameId":" 334a5258-4202-4205-8b74-dcc205feb566"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mta_nji-mno-mta"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mta"," userResponse":" mta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382885611","data":{"timestamp":" 947382885610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_045338"," gameId":" 334a5258-4202-4205-8b74-dcc205feb566"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mzu_mme-dha-mzu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mzu"," userResponse":" mzu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382891813","data":{"timestamp":" 947382891812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_045338"," gameId":" 334a5258-4202-4205-8b74-dcc205feb566"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nde_kwa-mwi-nde"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382898587","data":{"timestamp":" 947382898587"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_045338"," gameId":" 334a5258-4202-4205-8b74-dcc205feb566"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_mgo-mke-mki"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mki"," userResponse":" mki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947382904372","data":{"timestamp":" 947382904371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000109_045338"," gameId":" 334a5258-4202-4205-8b74-dcc205feb566"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_mgo-mke-mki"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}